# Denis Tsybulia

Batumi, Georgia

WhatsApp: https://wa.me/79219428310

Telegram: @dentsi

Phone: +995 558157151 E – mail: dentsi@yahoo.com

Skype: denis emis

(please contact WhatsUp or Telegram

messenger)

http://geo.emisdb.ru linkedin.com/in/denis-tsybulia



# Summary

Here is my recently reviewed detailed profile: http://geo.emisdb.ru.

I am a senior software engineer with 16 years of continuous experience in the web application development. Now based in Batumi, Republic of Georgia.

My main specialization is complex back-end web application with the ample use of interactive elements on modern platforms. Hereby I selected the most relevant to your project details of my 25 years long career.

My main technological stack is PHP development with the use of popular frameworks Yii and Laravel, using databases (MySQL, PostreSQL), server instruments (Memcached, Redis) and web-based platforms (Google Ad, Facebook Ads, Leadspedia) in a big variety of business fields.

Extensive experience of frontend development using HTML5, CSS, JS, JQuery, Bootstrap, numerous libraries like Google API, Yandex API, recently focus on Vue.JS.

Successfully completed 9 (3 in web) projects through individual effort and participated in 5 (all in web) big commercial ongoing projects as a team member during 25 years of my continuous career.

Extended version of this resume is available: http://geo.emisdb.ru/docs/cv eng g.pdf

#### Skills

- PHP Yii Yii2 Laravel Codeigniter Outsystems MySQL PostgreSQL
- JQuery, Ajax, JQuery UI, Google API, Yandex API
  Bootstrap
  Vue.js
  JavaScript
- Redis
  Memcached
  Docker
  Google Ads, Facebook ads, Leadspedia, Salesforce
- Remote Teamwork
  Git
  JIRA, Rally, Redmine
- Linux scripting
  C,C++
  Visual Basic and VBA
  QNX/Neutrino
- Fluent English, Good communication skills

# **Experience**



#### **Till** Senior Software Engineer

**NEKLO LLC** 

Jun 2023 - Nov 2023 (6 months)

Online Marketing Campaign Management Engine

### Senior Software Engineer

ГЦН-групп

Mar 2023 - May 2023 (3 months)

Application architecture builder and software developer Tasks: Mailing list dispatcher for business information system

# **\*** Senior Software Engineer

Invento Labs

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023 (4 months)

Web-based application for on-line psychological help.

#### web developer, PHP, Yii, Full Stack

ServiceCentral Technologies, Inc.

May 2020 - Jun 2022 (2 years 2 months)

Worked as a senior developer for the full-scale business information system for retail repair business: RepairQ.. https://repairq.io/

#### **PHP Web Developer**

Nash. travel: https://nash.travel/

Oct 2019 - Apr 2020 (7 months)

Worked as a system architecture and senior developer for the full-scale business

information system for hotel booking and property renting

## Senior Web Developer

eSystems Nordic

Apr 2016 - Oct 2019 (3 years 7 months)

Various project in the company with the use of Outsystems Platform

Technology: Outsystems Platform, HTML, JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax, Bootstrap 3 Description: Work as Software Engineer for various projects in the company.

# ♦ Senior Web Application Developer

Cherrytours

Oct 2015 - Apr 2016 (7 months)

Objective: Web-based full-scale tourist industry informational system

Description: Web-based information system for tourist industry. Worked as a system architecture and senior developer for the full-scale business information system

for tourist industry company.

# **Senior Web Application Developer**

**Termofit** 

May 2014 - Apr 2016 (2 years)

Objective: Web-based application for corporate business control system

Description: Web-based system for internal use. Back-end application for document flow

control, finance reporting and customer service control.

#### **Senior Web Application Developer**

Back-end web portal 2dmart

Mar 2014 - Dec 2014 (10 months)

Objective: The development of Internet-based applications such as "QR-code trade"

http://2dmart.com/ru/, http://dev.2dmart.com/dmart/

Description: Creation of the original web application for the operation of the registered

users system 2dmart. Web service provides sharing, search and implementation

of business processes to the trading on the basis of QR-code technology.

#### **Senior Software Engineer**

Elvis Advertising Agency

Mar 2012 - Nov 2014 (2 years 9 months)

Web-application for advertising company resources management:

http://bb .elvispiter.ru

Site engine was based on Yii Framework using JS and JQuery: eg Yandex Map API, JQuery UI.

#### **Senior Software Engineer**

Termofit

May 2005 - Apr 2012 (7 years)

The system of corporate accounting in a manufacturing enterprise was created and implemented. The system needed to develop and integrate a complex mechanism for the data exchange between different systems of accounting. The system works in the operation mode already within 10 years.

#### **Education**



Saint Petersburg State University

Sep 1993 - Jun 2000



The University of Alabama

exchange student Sep 1995 - May 1996